A Guide to the David Rockefeller papers, Associates, Warren T. Lindquist papers FA102
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1970 Accession, 1953-1975; 1
  - Planning Commission and State Downtown Plans: Working File, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 170)
    State of New York's plans for Battery Park City for developing the lower end of Manhattan compared with plans for same area developed by NYC Planning Commission.
  - Lower Manhattan Development: Richard Buford, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 171)
    City plan for developing lower end of Manhattan; Buford named director.
  - Battery Park City Authority, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 172)
    Real estate development in the Battery. State-organized body leased land from the city.
  - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association (D-LMA): General Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 173)
    Changes in association in personnel. Studies on changes in the area. 1962 resume of purpose and activities; DR chairman of the association. DR, WTL.
  - D-LMA: General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - D-LMA: Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 175)
    Newspaper stories on activity in area.
  - D-LMA: Committee on Membership, Organization, and Finance, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 176)
    Agenda; Staggered work hours.
  - D-LMA: Directors Meeting Minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - D-LMA: Historical Landmarks, 1962-1970 (Box 24, Folder 178)
    Proposals for preservation of South Street Seaport area and Fraunces Tavern.
  - D-LMA: Lower Manhattan Expressway Project, 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 179)
    WTL support of expressway, controversy.
  - D-LMA: Members Meeting Minutes, 1963-1969 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - D-LMA: Planning Committee Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 181)
  - D-LMA: Subway Study #1, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 182)
    Feasibility of Water Street Subway, 2nd Avenue Subway.
  - D-LMA: Subway Study #2, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - D-LMA: Subway Study #3, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 184)
  - D-LMA: Subway Study #4, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 185)
  - New York Stock Exchange: Correspondence and Notes, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 186)
    Search for a new home for the Exchange; WTL cooperation in efforts to reduce stock transfer tax.
  - New York Stock Exchange: Brochures and Clippings, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 187)
    New home and transfer tax.
  - New York Stock Exchange: Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 188)
    Work sheets on transfer tax.
  - World Trade Center: Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 190)
    Port Authority building proposed; DR support; controversy. WTL, DR, A. Tatin, L. Wein.
  - World Trade Center: Clippings, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 191)
  - World Trade Center: Reports and Statements, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 192)
    Descriptions of project; progress.
  - World Trade Center: Reports and Statements, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 193)
    Progress
  - Morningside Heights, Inc. Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 194)
  - Remedco: Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 195)
    Affiliate of Morningside Heights, sought to assist in development of area by using governmental agencies. Problems in managing residential properties. Loans to purchase property.
  - Remedco: Charter and By-laws, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 196)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: General Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 197)
    WTL participation on committee, DR contributions.
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 198)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Anniversary Dinner, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 199)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Board Meeting, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 200)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Finance Commitee, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 201)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: General, 1964-1966 (Box 28, Folder 202)
    WTL a member of committee and Vice President, Eastern Region; reports on activities and programs against discrimination; published studies on discrimination.
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: General, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 203)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Publications, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 204)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Publications, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 205)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Conferences, 1966; 1969 (Box 29, Folder 206)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: "Trends" newsletter, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 207)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: Clippings and Releases, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 208)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: White House Conference on the Aging: Housing Issues, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 209)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena, 1962-1965 (Box 29, Folder 210)
    DR, NAR, LSR purchase interest in Fazenda in 1962. WTL makes favorable report on property in 1965; plans for development inspection visits; DR purchased NAR interest in 1968; DR sold interest to R.O. Anderson in 1969. WTL, DR, NAR, LSR, Walther Moreira Salles.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 211)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 212)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 213)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1969 January-1969 July (Box 29, Folder 214)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1969 August-1969 December (Box 29, Folder 215)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 216)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Robert Anderson Stock Sale, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 217)
    Anderson's purchase of of DR's interest.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Approvals by DR, LSR, NAR, 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 218)
    Brothers' approvals of programs for Fazenda, and for sale of stock to DR.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Associates' Interests, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 219)
    Signed agreement of participation.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Robert Blocker, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 220)
    Represented DR in Brazil.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: By-Laws, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 221)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Clippings on Farming and Ranching, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 222)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Clippings on South America, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 223)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Covello Report of Operations, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 224)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: John Deere and Company, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 225)
    Contact with company, no action.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Documents, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 226)
    Cost system for evaluation, by-laws.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Exchange of Stock, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 227)
    Sale of LSR interests to DR.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Expenses, 1965-1969 (Box 31, Folder 228)
    Legal fees, travel, statements.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Expropriation, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 229)
    Brazilian legal provisions for expropriation.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Financial Statements, 1962-1967 (Box 31, Folder 230)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Financial Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 231)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Food Study, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 232)
    Study of possible interest ion Fazenda Bodoquena by Ralston Purina International.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: IPL Cattle Venture, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 233)
    Possible joint venture with King Ranch in Texas.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Meeting Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 234)
    J.A. Camargo visit to Fazenda 1968 and 1969; minutes from May 8 and June 2, 1969.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Personalities, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 235)
    Individuals connected with Fazenda.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Personnel and Staff, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 236)
    Comments on possible employees.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Proposed Pineapple Venture, 1966-1970 (Box 31, Folder 237)
    Proposed pineapple venture with Del Monte, did not work.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Inter-Office Memos and Notes, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 238)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Inter-Office Memos and Notes, 1967-1970 (Box 32, Folder 239)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Ralston Purina, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 240)
    Study of possible interest by Ralston Purina.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Background Reports, 1950s-1960s (Box 32, Folder 241)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Background Reports, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 242)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Registration Correspondence, 1966 August-1967 June (Box 33, Folder 243)
    Ending registration of NAR investment, increasing registration of DR investment on Fazenda.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Registration Correspondence, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 245)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Reports on Status and Feasibility, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 246)
    General studies on agricultural potential.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Reports on Status and Feasibility, 1963-1968 (Box 33, Folder 247)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Stanford Research Institute, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 248)
    Proposed study.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Squatters Land Reform, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 249)
    Eviction of settlers on company land.
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Statements of Income, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 250)
  - Fazenda Bodoquena: Statements of Income, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 251)
  - Westbay Community Associates: L.H. Larsen General File, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 252)
    Projections of property taxes; minutes; study, expenses and reports.
  - Westbay Community Associates: Clippings: Air Center or Westbay, 1967-1969 (Box 34, Folder 253)
    Controversy over Bay plans.
  - Westbay Community Associates: Clippings: Airport or Commerce, 1964-1969 (Box 34, Folder 254)
    Air traffic growth.
  - Westbay Community Associates: Clippings: Real Estate Development, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 255)
    Proposed plans for development.
  - Westbay Community Associates: Clippings: San Bruno, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 256)
    Controversy.
  - Westbay Community Associates: Clippings: Tidelands, Bay Fill, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 257)
  - Westbay: San Francisco Bay Conservation and Development Commission (BCDC): General Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 258)
    Commission-prepared overall plan for the development of the Bay. WTL speaking for Westbay Assoc. objected to many elements in the plan. Copy of study reports supporting the final plan.
  - Westbay: BCDE: General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 259)
  - Westbay: BCDC: San Francisco Bay Plan and Supplement, 1969 January (Box 35, Folder 260)
  - Westbay: Pacific Air Commerce Center (PACC): Board of Directors, 1963-1966 (Box 35, Folder 261)
    Joint venture between DR, Crocker Land Company, and others to build in San Francisco Bay. Minutes of Board meetings.
  - Westbay: PACC: Solicitation for Contracts, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 262)
    Offers to work on PACC project by contractors and architects.
  - Westbay: PACC: Public Relations, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 263)
    Efforts to explain bay filling projects; changing forms of attacks; decision to delay all action until court decision on ownership of tidelands.
  - Westbay: PACC: Legislation on Tidal Plain Zoning, 1963-1969 (Box 35, Box 264)
    Copies of California laws; legislative activity; 1969 law regulating use of tidelands.
  - Westbay: PACC: "Love Letters" Objections to Tide Lands Plan, 1966-1969 (Box 35, Folder 265)
    Objections to plans for filling in San Francisco Bay tidelands; Associates replies.
  - Westbay: PACC: Stockholders, 1963-1965 (Box 36, Folder 266)
    Memo of understanding from September 20, 1963, between DR, Crocker Land Company, and the Ideal Cement Company; minutes of stockholders meetings; by-laws; alterations in agreement; change to Westbay Associates.
  - Westbay: PACC: Stockholders, 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 267)
    Minutes of stockholders meetings; by-laws; alterations in agreement; change to Westbay Associates.
  - Westbay: PACC: Lindquist Statements and Presentations, 1963-1969 (Box 36, Folder 268)
    Copies of statements by WTL; lists of meetings attended to present Westbay Associates case; attendees.
  - Westbay: San Bruno: Charts and Maps, 1964-1967 (Box 36, Folder 269)
  - Westbay: San Bruno: Names and Contacts, 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 270)
    Identification of people involved in the project.
  - Westbay: San Bruno: Fill Feasibility Study, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 271)
    Arranging for study; statement of problems and objectives.
  - Westbay: San Bruno: Planning and Development, 1964, 1968-1969; 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 272)
    Housing possibilities on San Bruno Mountain.
  - Westbay: Robert Cranmer Correspondence with Warren Lindquist, 1966-1972 (Box 36, Folder 273)
    Cranmer was project manager in San Francisco who kept WTL informed on changes and prospects.
  - Westbay: Robert Cranmer Correspondence with all, 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 274)
    Reports on studies; progress of planning; relations with official organizations
  - Westbay: Structure of Joint Venture, 1963-1967 (Box 36, Folder 275)
    Agreements between partners; changes in structure; change in name
  - Westbay: Expenses and Finances, 1962-1970 (Box 37, Folder 276)
    Payments for services and studies performed; financial statements; tax problems.
  - Westbay: Ideal Cement Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 37, Folder 277)
    Information on Ideal Cement; merger with American Potash into Ideal Basic Industries, Inc.
  - Westbay: Ideal Cement Legal Documents and Consents, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 278)
  - Westbay: Inter-Office Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 37, Folder 279)
    Developing program; reports on progress; legal statements.
  - Westbay: Warren T. Lindquist Itineraries, 1965-1969 (Box 37, Folder 280)
  - Westbay: Jericho Bay, 1965-1970 (Box 37, Folder 281)
    Participating corporation for JDR 3rd and Abby Mauze in San Francisco Bay fill project. Minutes of meetings.
  - Westbay: Litigation, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 282)
    City ordinance regulations; studies of state laws; question of ownership of submerged lands.
  - Westbay: Partnership Meeting Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 283)
  - Westbay: Pacific Cement Aggregates: Lease, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 284)
    Agreements regulating the amount of quarry activity to be conducted outside the joint venture.
  - Westbay: Warrent T. Lindquist Presentation File, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 285)
    Used by Lindquist in meetings.
  - Westbay: Public Relations, 1963-1966 (Box 38, Folder 286)
    Statements made; position papers; Saul Richman memorandum on P.R.; WTL statements; Alan Temko articles.
  - Westbay PR: Warrent T. Lindquist Remarks to San Francisco Board of Directors Dinner, 1964 February 19 (Box 38, Folder 287)
  - Westbay PR: Warrent T. Lindquist Letters to Brugmann and Mott, 1964 November (Box 38, Folder 288)
  - Westbay PR: PACC Events, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 289)
  - Westbay PR: PACC Positions, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 290)
  - Westbay PR: PACC Publicity, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 291)
  - Westbay PR: Saul Richman Memo on San Mateo County Bay Shore Project, 1963 June (Box 38, Folder 292)
  - Westbay PR: Warrent T. Lindquist Memo to Belford Brown, 1963 November 21 (Box 38, Folder 293)
  - Westbay PR: Warren T. Lindquist Statement to San Francisco Public Utilities Commission, 1964 January 28 (Box 38, Folder 294)
  - Westbay PR: Ideal Cement Co. Statement to San Francisco Bay Conservation Study Commission, 1964 November 28 (Box 38, Folder 295)
  - Westbay PR: Belford Brown: Airport and Tidelands, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 296)
  - Westbay PR: Save the San Francisco Bay Association, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 297)
  - Westbay PR: Allan Temko Articles, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 298)
  - Westbay: Stallings and Associates, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 299)
  - Westbay: Reports from Consultants, 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 300)
    Studies of San Bruno mountain, housing development, incline elevators.
  - Westbay: Reports from Consultants, 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 301)
  - Westbay: Reports from Consultants, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 302)
  - Westbay: San Francisco Philanthropic Requests, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 303)
    Only request is from St. Francis Hospital.
  - Westbay: Material for David Rockefeller's Interview with Mayor Earl Selby, 1968 November-December (Box 39, Folder 304)
    WTL lists for interview with mayor.
  - Westbay: Formal Documents, 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 305)
    Documents used to develop rights for Westbay program; joint venture agreements.
  - Westbay: Formal Documents, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 306)
  - Westbay: San Quintin, Mexico, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 307)
    Proposed Mexican venture for partners; not done.
  - Westbay: Tartan Bay, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 39, Folder 308)
    Corporate entity holding DR's equity in Westbay Connnunity Associates; minutes of meetings; payment of expenses.
  - Westbay: Tax Returns and Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 39, Folder 309)
    Copies of Federal and California returns.
  - Westbay: Title Clearance, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 310)
    Opposition to leveling San Bruno mountain; title company reports.
  - Westbay: San Francisco Airport, 1963-1968 (Box 40, Folder 311)
  - Westbay: PACC Reference Material, 1967-1969 (Box 40, Folder 312)
  - Westbay: PACC Tidelands Reclamation Report Appendices, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 313)
  - Possible Appearances by David Rockefeller, 1960-1968 (Box 40, Folder 314)
    Memoranda re: organizations issuing invitations--most declined; rough drafts.
  - Business Committee for Social Progress, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 315)
    DR address for annual conference of Business Executives Institute October 26, 1963; clippings; proposal for Business Committee for Social Progress; proposed memo of commitment; 1968 Experimental Public Affairs Forecast.
  - New York State Urban Development Corporation (UDC), 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 316)
    Outline of Joint Corporation to combine State and private resources; proposals; creation of NYS Urban Development Corporation in 1968; ABT Association report on industrial loft development; residential project procedure, projects proposed; estimated costs.
  - New York State UDC, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 317)
  - New York State UDC, 1967-1970 (Box 41, Folder 318)
  - New York State UDC: Tretter and Urstadt Drafts, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 319)
    Proposed housing foundation; Urban Development Corporation plans; outline comparison of the housing proposals.
  - New York State UDC: Lindquist Memo on Joint Corporation, 1966 December (Box 41, Folder 320)
  - New York State UDC: Prospective Staff for Joint Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 321)
    Selection of Charles Urstadt; candidates for Board of Joint Corporation; list of experts in urban development; Urban Development Corporation officers.
  - New York State UDC: Clippings on Joint Corporation, 1967-1970 (Box 41, Folder 322)
    Re: space shortage, exodus of companies from NYC, lack of funds for housing and business loans; press releases and articles; UDC/Westchester County Agreement.
  - Channel 13, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 323)
    EBC operations; program re Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association and World Trade Center; clippings.
  - International Executive Service Corps, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 324)
    DR founded this service group. Article; by-laws, certificate of incorporation.
  - Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 325)
    Clippings re: DR statement before Senate Banking Committee and EEOC.
  - Governor Nelson Rockefeller's Urban Position, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 326)
    NAR speech "The Making of a Just America"; memo re: Federal Programs for Financing Capital Development of Cities.
  - Council of Housing Producers, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 327)
    Press releases, background information.
  - Minutes of Meetings of LSR's Resort Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 328)
    Extracts relating to DR's interests in St. Croix.
  - Real Estate Computer Program, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 329)
    Experimental use of computers in real estate management.
  - AID Investment and Guaranty Program, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 330)
    Index to Catalog of Investment Information and Opportunities January 1966; CMB foreign trade service bulletins; investment guaranty agreements; specific risk investment guaranty handbook.
  - Dinty Moore's Restaurant, 1963-1967 (Box 42, Folder 331)
    Charge faci1ities obtaines in 1963, expenses.
  - Rockefeller Center Lunch Club, 1960-1967 (Box 42, Folder 332)
    WTL membership; yearly statements of Club; charges and payment; WTL resignation in 1966.
  - 1 Chase Manhattan Plaza, 1965-1969 (Box 43, Folder 333)
    Expense accounts and statements. Larsen, O'Brien, WTL, JRHB.
  - 1 Chase Manhattan Plaza, 1965-1969 (Box 43, Folder 334)
  - Morningside Heights: Printed Material, 1955-1965 (Box 43, Folder 335-338)
  - New York Housing and Planning: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 44, Folder 339-341)
  - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 44, Folder 342-343)
  - D-LMA: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 344-345)
  - Port Authority: Printed Material on World Trade Center, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 346)
  - Port Authority: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 45, Folder 347)
  - Transportation/Bridge Authorities: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 348-349)
  - Chase Manhattan: Printed Material, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 350)
  - Embarcadero Center: Printed Material, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 351-352)
  - Embarcadero Center: Printed Material, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 353-354)
  - Pacific Air Commerce Center (PACC): Printed Material, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 355-356)
  - San Bruno Mountain: Printed Material, 1962, 1968; 1968 (Box 48, Folder 357)
  - Westbay Refill: Printed Material, 1962-1969 (Box 48, Folder 358-360)
  - Printed Oversized Material, 1960-1977 (Box 88, Folder 769)
    Embarcadero Center; regional planning reports; Westbay Associates; World Trade Center.
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1953 August-1955 December (Box 48, Folder 361-362)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1956 January-1958 July (Box 49, Folder 363-369)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1958 August-1959 July (Box 50, Folder 370-379)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1959 August-1960 August (Box 51, Folder 380-389)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1960 September-1961 June (Box 52, Folder 390-399)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1961 July-1962 August (Box 53, Folder 400-412)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1962 September-1963 July (Box 54, Folder 413-423)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1963 August-1964 October (Box 55, Folder 424-435)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1964 November-1965 October (Box 56, Folder 436-446)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1965 November-1966 August (Box 57, Folder 447-456)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1966 September-1967 July (Box 58, Folder 457-467)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1967 August-1968 July (Box 59, Folder 468-479)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1968 August-1969 July (Box 60, Folder 480-491)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1969 August-1972 November (Box 61, Folder 492-505)
  - Warren T. Lindquist Chronological File, 1972 December-1975 August (Box 62, Folder 506-516)
  - John Spencer Chronological File, 1961 October-1962 January (Box 62, Folder 517)
- 1978 Accession, 1960-1977; 2
  - American Arbitration Association, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 518)
  - Arbitration: Sky Villa Motel, 1975-1977 (Box 63, Folder 519)
  - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 520)
  - Battery Park City Task Force, 1972-1977 (Box 63, Folder 521-525)
    General correspondence; meeting materials; convention center proposal.
  - Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 526)
  - Brooklyn, New York, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 527)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: General, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 528-532)
  - Business-Labor Working Group: Economic Development Task Force Meeting, 1976 March (Box 64, Folder 533)